Look brother, the sheet on this side of our machine is also ready.
Now you just have to make a circle of the size of the die,
but one thing to keep in mind brother, the
circle should not be even slightly bigger.
Otherwise the paper will get stuck in it again and again.
That's why brother, I
first made a circle by placing this die on the sheet.  Then by
fitting the die in it, the sphere was made of a perfectly fixed size.
Now brother, you just have to pick up the die
and put it in the machine.  This
sheet also has to be placed over it.  Then will
both start happening just by turning this switch?  Oh no
brother, first put the roll at the back and take
out the paper and take it to the die.  Then when you
rotate it, it will come out as a bowl.  Why are
two plates being made together?  From now on,
two rolls of plates will be made in a day.